bestxtube.com 2011-10-07

# Privacy Policy - Best X Tube

We at Best X Tube take very seriously the private nature of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how we handle the information we collect when you visit our site and/or become a member. Please read this notice carefully.

Best X Tube is an online adult-oriented community where you can view and contribute adult content, and interact and communicate with others. Beyond what you choose to share, we will never use, sell, share or disclose your personal information, except as described here, or as may be required by law.

## Information We Receive and Store

  1. Information Logged By Best X Tube 

We also log certain non-personally-identifiable information, including the Internet Protocol (“IP”) address assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider, aggregate user data, and browser type, as you visit our site or use our service.

  2. Cookies 

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. Like most sites, we use cookies to store user and visitor data and to record session information. Additionally, our advertisers may set cookies (“Advertiser Cookies”) to allow an ad server to recognize your computer each time the advertiser sends you an online advertisement.

## Use and Disclosure of Information We Collect

We will use and disclose your information only as follows:

We may use your session data, etc., to improve our site and/or tailor your experience at our site, showing you content that we think you might be interested in. Non-personally-identifiable information may be shared, in aggregate, anonymous form, with third parties, such as advertisers, to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members; this shared information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.

Best X Tube may process personally identifying information for such purposes as:

  * Providing you with information related to your Best X Tube account or our other sites and services; 
  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services; 
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and 
  * Developing new services. 

Our cookies are used to enhance the user experience, and to focus advertising. Users may be able to configure their browser to accept or reject cookies, or notify the user when a cookie is set. It is the user's responsibility to set browser preferences regarding cookies, although you should be aware that disabling cookies will affect performance and functionality of our site. Advertisers may use Advertiser Cookies to gather information about where you accessed their advertisements and to determine which ads you clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver focused advertisements that they believe will be of the most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Best X Tube itself and does not cover the use of Advertiser Cookies by any advertisers.

Other information logged by Best X Tube is used to help manage our website and provide a better user experience, to track usage, to focus advertising and in the case of IP addresses, for security and monitoring purposes.

Except as set forth above, we will disclose your information to third parties only as reasonably required to protect the legal rights of us, our shareholders, members, employees and customers (such as legal representatives and law enforcement), as you expressly permit, and as required by law (such as the result of a court subpoena). We may transfer your information in the event of a sale of substantially all of the assets of our business to a third-party or in the event of a merger, consolidation or acquisition. However, in such event, any acquirer will be subject to the provisions of our commitments to you. We will never provide, share, rent, trade or sell user-specific personal information to any third party marketers, unless you ask us to. 

## Miscellaneous

### Location of Servers and Information

Best X Tube processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and/or abroad. For users outside the United States, please note that any personally-identifying information you enter into the Best X Tube site will be transferred out of your country and into the United States. You consent to such transfer through your use of the Site and our Services. You also warrant that you have the right to transfer such information outside your country and into the United States. For users within the United States, you consent to the transfer of information beyond domestic orders through your use of the Site and our Services.

### Third Party Links

You may encounter links to other sites on Best X Tube. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site, you should read the privacy policy appearing on that site. 

### Notification of Changes

Any changes in our Privacy Policy will be posted to this website and will become effective as of the date of posting with respect to information we then collect in the future, but will not be changed with respect to information that we have then already collected. It is and will be your responsibility to review our Privacy Policy from time to time to make sure you are aware of any changes.

### Effective Date

This Privacy Policy is effective with respect to all data that we have collected since the date we started collecting data which was November 10, 2009.

### Contacting Us

We take our users' privacy extremely seriously, and we have adopted policies and practices that will keep the private information you provide to us safe. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, our practices, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: [privacy@bestxtube.com](mailto:privacy@bestxtube.com).
